Okay, now I'm going to show you a quick demo on the rag observability and monitoring and earlier,
if you remember, we had discussed there are two types of logs in bedrock knowledge base.
So let's go ahead and explore how we can monitor this through the cloud watch.
So this is a knowledge base we had created in the previous lecture.
So what I can do is I can just go to this demo bedrock kB001 and just click on this edit here
and then you can see log deliveries. So I can just say add to Amazon cloud watch logs to Amazon
S3 to Amazon data firehouse. So I'll just click on to Amazon cloud watch logs and here it
automatically creates a log group. So just remember it ends with QBU and I'll just say add.
Okay, now it has added this log group. So if I just click on this log group, it will
take me to cloud watch logs. Now you can see there's nothing in this log group at this point of time.
Now what I'm going to do is I'm going to make a little change. So I'll just go to this S3 bucket
and upload one more document. So this is my data source. So I'll just click on this AWS overview.
It just gives you an overview of all the AWS services. So let me just click on upload.
So it's going to take a few minutes. Okay. Now everything has been uploaded. Okay. Now this document
has been uploaded. Now let me just go back to the knowledge base. So I'm here on the knowledge base.
Let me just go here. So we have to sync the data. Now what we have to do is we have to sync the
data. So let me just click on this knowledge base and you can see here sync. So I'll just click on
this sync and it's good to resync. So what sync basically does is when we add new data to the
knowledge base, it will do the chunking, then it will create vector embeddings, store it in the
vector store and do all that behind the scenes. So every time you add new data, you have to
do a resync. Now it has completely synced. So now if I just go back to the cloud watch,
I should be able to see some logs. And you can see now these logs have been generated.
So if I just click on this and let's see some of the logs that are getting generated.
So you can see ingestion jobs started and number of resources and there's some parameters here.
And then so it's showing as event timestamp, then ingestion job ID, what was the source data
location, data sources. And then if you just click, it will show you more details on see here
it's showing as embedding started and then it will show stored in the vector store and so on.
So it will show you all the jobs that have been run, you know, all the processes that it has
followed, which is the data source document uploaded chunking done, vector embedding done,
and if I just continue and it will show you till this job is complete. So if anything fails,
you will be able to see it here. So what you can do is you can monitor all of these statistics
here. So if any resource fails or any part of the process fails, and then you can set up cloud watch
plums. So one last thing I want to highlight is for these resource logs. So just remember because
these resource logs also use a large language model to generate a response to a query. So a
respective of where you are invoking the model from, whether it's from the console here on the
playground or you have built an application using API gateway lambda and Amazon bedrock or through a
rack system, your logs would be stored in the log group. You have configured here under this setting
and earlier we had seen that we had configured the logs under this log group name demo underscore
bedrock underscore monitoring. So irrespective of wherever you send the prompt to the foundation
model, they would be logged here in this particular log group. Okay, so that's pretty much it from
from this lecture as in the next lecture, thank you.